A Guide to the Records of the Arlington County Civic Federation, 1928-2008
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Records of the Arlington County Civic Federation, 1928-2008
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
RG 14
42 boxes.
Arlington County Civic Federation
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Various Civic Federation members have made donations to this collection in 1982, 1989, 1997, 2002, 2008, 2010, and 2018.
Historical Information
Founded in 1916 and still active, the Arlington County Civic Federation is a non partisan organization composed of member community organizations. Each member association "sends delegates to meetings to discuss and adopt positions or resolutions on community civic matters that affect Arlington County and its citizens." The Federation has no official status nor is it part of the local government. Through its member organizations, meetings, and numerous committees, the Federation has been responsible for educating local citizens about major issues affecting the county and has played an active role in bringing about major improvements throughout the county. The Federation has also served as one of the county government "watchdogs" through monitoring and influencing County Board decisions and actions. The Federation presents citizens' collective views to the Board on issues which include zoning, schools, libraries, parks, police, taxes, transportation, development, and planning.
Scope and Content
Record Group 14 houses the records of the Arlington County Civic Federation, a federation of Arlington County local neighborhood civic associations. The collection dates from 1928 through 2008 and houses such records as the Federation's general and executive committee minutes and meeting files, committee reports, committee files, subject correspondence files, lists of delegates and officers, financial records, bulletins, annual banquet files, and other records. A complete listing of the record series is attached. The collection measures approximately 17 linear feet.
These records present a valuable resource to researchers interested in most aspects of Arlington County history and development. Subgroup 3, Activities, and Subgroup 5, Office of the Secretary, Tommye Morton, house meeting minutes and committee reports that represent an almost intact record of all Federation activities from 1928 through 2008. The committee files and subject files arranged in Subgroup 3 house additional information regarding issues, activities, and the relationship of the Federation to the county board and local government for the period of 1943 through the early 2000s. Of particular interest are the committee files on zoning and community development. Lists of the Federation committees and the subject files are attached to this finding aid. Information regarding the structure and organization of the Federation is located in Subgroup 1, Organization.
Arrangement
Record Group 14 is arranged into seven subgroups, based on broad functional categories. Within Subgroups 1, 2, 3, and 4, records series have been established according to type of material. Most of the file units are in rough chronological order. The correspondence in Subgroup 3, Series 7, was originally in binders with the executive committee minutes (Subgroup 3, Series 2) for the designated years. Subgroup 5 is the donated records of the Secretary of the ACCF, Tommye Morton. The records have been maintained in the original order of one file for each month and a file for a yearly index. Often the index file also has a list of Federation delegates. The material includes meeting minutes, correspondence, and agendas and covers the dates December 1986 through June 1995. The files for the months of January 1987 and January 1991 are missing. Subgroup 6, Financial Materials, consists of financial files for the Federation, 1961-2007. Subgroup 7, Arlington County Official Publications, consists of county publications collected by the Federation, apparently for study. Folders containing photographs have an asterisk [*] after the file name.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Community Archives hold the records of many different county organizations that are members of the Civic Federation. Please contact a CLH staff member or check the library catalog for our collection holdings. RG 32, County Manager's Library, contains Civic Federation material from their schools committee.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Citizens' associations; Community organization.; Neighborhoods.; Arlington County (Va.); Arlington (Va.)
Contents List
- Organization
  - Constitution & By-Laws
    - 1939-1984, 1994 (Box 1)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 1)
    - 1998, 2001, 2003, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Lists of Officers and Committees
    - 1916-1985 (Box 1)
    - 1916-1987 (Box 1)
  - Committee Structure
    - 1967 (Box 1)
  - Lists of Member Association Presidents
    - 1952-1985 (Box 1)
  - Lists of Delegates and Alternates
    - 1941-1959 (Box 1)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 1)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 1)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - 1969 (Box 1)
    - 1970-1986 (Box 2)
  - Member Association Files, 1941-1980
    - Maps, Neighbor Associations (Box 2)
    - Arlington Heights Constitution & Bylaws (Box 2)
    - Arlington Ridge (Box 2)
    - Arlington Education Association (Box 2)
    - Arlington Forest (Box 2)
    - American Association of University Women (Box 2)
    - Ballston Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Barcroft School & Civic League (Box 2)
    - Bellevue Forest Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Boulevard Manor Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Central Arlington Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Chamber of Commerce - Junior (Box 2)
    - Cherrydale Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Citizens Committee for School Improvement (Box 2)
    - Claremont Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Columbia Heights (Box 2)
    - Colombia Pike Citizens Association (Box 2)
    - Courtland Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Dominion Hills/Paisley Forest (Box 2)
    - Donaldson Run Civic Association (Box 2)
    - East Falls Church Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Fairlington Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Forest Glen Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Fort Myer Heights Civic Association (Box 2)
    - Glencarlyn (Box 2)
    - Lyon Park (Box 2)
    - Lyon Village (Box 2)
    - Gulf Branch (Box 3)
    - Leeway Gardens (Box 3)
    - Madison Manor (Box 3)
    - Maywood (Box 3)
    - Nauck (Box 3)
    - New Arlington (Box 3)
    - Northwest Arlington (Box 3)
    - Northwest Arlington - Newsletters (Box 3)
    - North Highlands (Box 3)
    - Old Glebe (Box 3)
    - Organized Women Voters (Box 3)
    - Parkway (Box 3)
    - Rivercrest (Box 3)
    - Rock Spring (Box 3)
    - Stonewall Jackson (Box 3)
    - Tara-Leeway Heights (Box 3)
    - Tower Villas (Box 3)
    - Walker Chapel (Box 3)
    - Washington & Lee (Box 3)
    - Westover (Box 3)
    - Williamsburg (Box 3)
    - Highland Park-Overlee Knolls (Box 3)
- Office of the President
  - Clarence Salisbury's Files
    - 1966 (Box 3)
  - W. M. Graham's Files
    - 1968 (Box 3)
  - Anne Noll's Files, 1975-1989
    - General Files (Box 3)
    - Committee of 100 (Box 3)
    - Workshop-County Action Plan Services to Limited English-Speaking Persons, May, 1985 (Box 3)
    - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers (Box 4)
    - Public Access TV in Arlington (Box 4)
    - Center for Urban Education Incorporated (Box 4)
    - Arlington County Department of Libraries (Box 4)
    - Park Bond Referendum, 1981-1984 (Box 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, "Arlington Horticulture News," 1979 (Box 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, Virginia Technical University, "Home and Garden Notes," 1972-1981 (Box 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, Arlington "Newsletter," 1972-1979 (Box 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Service Publications (Box 4)
  - President's Reports
    - President's Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Board Material (Box 4)
- Activities
  - Regular Minutes and Meeting Files
    - December 1928 - June 1929 (Box 5)
    - July - December 1929 (Box 5)
    - 1930 (Box 5)
    - 1931 (Box 5)
    - 1932 (Box 5)
    - January - November 1933 (Box 5)
    - 1934 (Box 5)
    - January - June 1935 (Box 5)
    - 1935 (Box 5)
    - 1942 (Box 5)
    - January - June 1943 (Box 5)
    - September - December 1943 (Box 5)
    - January - June 1944 (Box 5)
    - September - December 1944 (Box 5)
    - January - March 1945 (Box 5)
    - April - June 1945 (Box 5)
    - September - December 1945 (Box 5)
    - January - March 1946 (Box 6)
    - April - June 1946 (Box 6)
    - September - December 1946 (Box 6)
    - January - March 1947 (Box 6)
    - April - June 1947 (Box 6)
    - September - December 1947 (Box 6)
    - January - March 1948 (Box 6)
    - March - June 1948 (Box 6)
    - September - December 1948 (Box 6)
    - January - April 1949 (Box 6)
    - May - September 1949 (Box 6)
    - October - December 1949 (Box 6)
    - January - February 1950 (Box 6)
    - March - April 1950 (Box 7)
    - May - June 1950 (Box 7)
    - September - December 1950 (Box 7)
    - January - March 1951 (Box 7)
    - March - June 1951 (Box 7)
    - September - October 1951 (Box 7)
    - November - December 1951 (Box 7)
    - January - February 1952 (Box 7)
    - March - April 1952 (Box 7)
    - May - June 1952 (Box 7)
    - September - November 1952 (Box 7)
    - December 1952 (Box 7)
    - January - February 1953 (Box 7)
    - March - April 1953 (Box 7)
    - May - June 1953 (Box 7)
    - September - December 1953 (Box 7)
    - January - February 1954 (Box 7)
    - March - April 1954 (Box 8)
    - May - June 1954 (Box 8)
    - September - October 1954 (Box 8)
    - November - December 1954 (Box 8)
    - January - February 1955 (Box 8)
    - March - April 1955 (Box 8)
    - May - June 1955 (Box 8)
    - September - December 1955 (Box 8)
    - January - February 1956 (Box 8)
    - March - April 1956 (Box 8)
    - May - June 1956 (Box 8)
    - September - October 1956 (Box 8)
    - November - December 1956 (Box 8)
    - January - February 1957 (Box 8)
    - March - April 1957 (Box 8)
    - May - June 1957 (Box 8)
    - September - October 1957 (Box 8)
    - November - December 1957 (Box 8)
    - January - February 1958 (Box 8)
    - March - April 1958 (Box 8)
    - May - June 1958 (Box 8)
    - September - October 1958 (Box 8)
    - November - December 1958 (Box 8)
    - January - February 1959 (Box 8)
    - March - April 1959 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1959 (Box 9)
    - September - October 1959 (Box 9)
    - November - December 1959 (Box 9)
    - January - February 1960 (Box 9)
    - March - April 1960 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1960 (Box 9)
    - September - October 1960 (Box 9)
    - November - December 1960 (Box 9)
    - January - February 1961 (Box 9)
    - March - April 1961 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1961 (Box 9)
    - September - October 1961 (Box 9)
    - November - December 1961 (Box 9)
    - January - February 1962 (Box 9)
    - March - April 1962 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1962 (Box 9)
    - September - October 1962 (Box 9)
    - November - December 1962 (Box 9)
    - January - February 1963 (Box 9)
    - March - April 1963 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1963 (Box 9)
    - September - December 1963 (Box 9)
    - January - February 1964 (Box 9)
    - March - April 1964 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1964 (Box 9)
    - September - October 1964 (Box 9)
    - November - December 1964 (Box 9)
    - January - February 1965 (Box 9)
    - March - April 1965 (Box 9)
    - May - June 1965 (Box 9)
    - September - October 1965 (Box 10)
    - November - December 1965 (Box 10)
    - January - March 1966 (Box 10)
    - April - June 1966 (Box 10)
    - September - December 1966 (Box 10)
    - January - March 1967 (Box 10)
    - April - June 1967 (Box 10)
    - September - December 1967 (Box 10)
    - 1968 (Box 10)
    - January - November 1969 (Box 10)
    - January - October 1970 (Box 10)
    - January - February 1971 (Box 10)
    - March - April 1971 (Box 10)
    - May - June 1971 (Box 10)
    - September - December 1971 (Box 10)
    - January - March 1972 (Box 10)
    - April - June 1973 (Box 10)
    - September - December 1972 (Box 10)
    - January - May 1973 (Box 10)
    - June - December 1973 (Box 10)
    - January - June 1974 (Box 10)
    - September - December 1974 (Box 10)
    - January - May 1975 (Box 10)
    - June 1975 (Box 10)
    - September - October 1975 (Box 10)
    - November - December 1975 (Box 10)
    - January - February 1976 (Box 10)
    - March - May 1976 (Box 10)
    - June 1976 (Box 10)
    - September - December 1976 (Box 11)
    - January - March 1977 (Box 11)
    - April - May, September 1977 (Box 11)
    - January - June 1978 (Box 11)
    - 1979 (Box 11)
    - January - June 1980 (Box 11)
    - June - December 1980 (Box 11)
    - January - May 1981 (Box 11)
    - June - December 1981 (Box 11)
    - 1982 (Box 11)
    - 1983 (Box 11)
    - 1984 (Box 12)
    - January - May 1985 (Box 12)
    - June - December 1985 (Box 12)
    - January - March 1986 (Box 12)
    - April - December 1986 (Box 12)
    - 1987 (Box 12)
    - July 1995 - February 1996 (Box 12)
    - March - June 1996 (Box 12)
    - September - December 1996 (Box 13)
    - April - June 1997 (Box 13)
    - September - October 1997 (Box 13)
    - November 1997 - February 1998 (Box 13)
    - March - June 1998 (Box 13)
    - September 1998 - February 1999 (Box 14)
    - March - June 1999 (Box 14)
    - September 1999 - January 2000 (Box 14)
    - February - June 2000 (Box 14)
    - September 2000 - February 2001 (Box 14)
    - March 2001 - June 2001 (Box 14)
    - September 2001 - February 2002 (Box 14)
    - March - June 2002 (Box 15)
    - September 2002 - February 2003 (Box 15)
    - March - June 2003 (Box 15)
    - July 2003 - February 2004 (Box 15)
    - March - June 2004 (Box 15)
    - August - November 2004 (Box 15)
    - December 2004 - June 2005 (Box 15)
  - Executive Committee Minutes
    - November 1928 - November 1929 (Box 16)
    - 1942 (Box 16)
    - 1943 (Box 16)
    - 1944 (Box 16)
    - 1945 (Box 16)
    - 1946 (Box 16)
    - 1947 (Box 16)
    - 1948 (Box 16)
    - 1949 (Box 16)
    - 1950 (Box 16)
    - 1951 (Box 16)
    - 1952 (Box 16)
    - 1953 (Box 16)
    - 1954 (Box 16)
    - 1955 (Box 16)
    - 1956 (Box 16)
    - 1957 (Box 16)
    - 1958 (Box 16)
    - 1959 (Box 16)
    - 1960 (Box 16)
    - 1961 (Box 16)
    - 1962 (Box 16)
    - 1963 (Box 16)
    - 1964 (Box 16)
    - 1965 (Box 16)
    - 1966 (Box 16)
    - 1967 (Box 16)
    - 1968 (Box 16)
    - 1969 (Box 16)
    - 1970 (Box 16)
    - 1971 (Box 16)
    - 1972 (Box 16)
    - 1973 (Box 16)
    - 1974 (Box 16)
    - 1975 (Box 16)
    - 1976 (Box 16)
    - 1977 (Box 16)
    - 1978 (Box 16)
    - 1979 (Box 17)
    - 1980 (Box 17)
    - 1981 (Box 17)
    - 1949-1955 (Box 17)
    - 1949 (Box 17)
    - 1982 (Box 17)
    - 1983 (Box 17)
    - 1984 (Box 17)
    - 1985 (Box 17)
    - 1986 (Box 17)
    - 1987 (Box 17)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 17)
    - June 1994 - June 1995 (Box 17)
    - July 1995 - September 1995 (Box 17)
    - October 1995 - February 1996 (Box 18)
    - March - June 1996 (Box 18)
    - July - December 1996 (Box 18)
    - January - June 1997 (1) (Box 18)
    - January - June 1997 (2) (Box 18)
    - July 1997 - June 1998 (1) (Box 18)
    - July 1997 - June 1998 (2) (Box 19)
    - July 1998 - June 1999 (Box 19)
    - July 1999 - June 2000 (1) (Box 19)
    - July 1999 - June 2000 (2) (Box 19)
    - July 2000 - March 2001 (1) (Box 19)
    - July 2000 - March 2001 (2) (Box 19)
    - April - June 2001 (Box 19)
    - July 2001 - June 2002 (Box 19)
    - July 2002 - June 2003 (Box 20)
    - July 2003 - June 2004 (Box 20)
    - July 2004 - June 2005 (Box 20)
    - July 2005 - June 2006 (Box 20)
    - July 2006 - June 2007 (Box 20)
    - July 2007 - June 2008 (1) (Box 20)
    - July 2007 - June 2008 (2) (Box 20)
  - Committee Files, 1943-1986
    - Adhoc Advisory Committee - Fire Service (Box 20)
    - Arlington Citizen's Participation Council (Box 20)
    - Beautification and Landscape Committee (Box 20)
    - Bond Issues, Citizen's Advisory Committee (Box 21)
    - Community Development Committee (1) (Box 21)
    - Community Development Committee (2) (Box 21)
    - Community Development Committee (3) (Box 21)
    - Constitution and By-Laws Committee (Box 21)
    - Environmental Committee (Box 21)
    - Health and Welfare Committee (1) (Box 21)
    - Health and Welfare Committee (2) (Box 21)
    - Legislation and Legal Action Committee (1) (Box 21)
    - Legislation and Legal Action Committee (2) (Box 21)
    - Highways Committee (Box 21)
    - Housing Committee (Box 21)
    - Interfederation Council (Box 21)
    - Journal Trophy Committee (Box 22)
    - Libraries Committee (1) (Box 22)
    - Libraries Committee (2) (Box 22)
    - Local Government Committee (1) (Box 22)
    - Local Government Committee (2) (Box 22)
    - Membership Committee (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - National Capital Planning Commission (Box 22)
    - Neighborhood Conservation Advisory Committee (Box 22)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 22)
    - Planning and Zoning Committee (Box 22)
    - Public Safety Committee (1) (Box 22)
    - Public Safety Committee (2) (Box 22)
    - Public Utilities Committee (1) (Box 22)
    - Public Utilities Committee (2) (Box 23)
    - Public Welfare Advisory Committee (Box 23)
    - Publicity Committee (Box 23)
    - Special Committee on Race Relations (Box 23)
    - Recreation Committee (1) (Box 23)
    - Recreation Committee (2) (Box 23)
    - Revenues and Expenditures Committee (1) (Box 23)
    - Revenues and Expenditures Committee (2) (Box 23)
    - Revenues and Expenditures Committee (3) (Box 23)
    - Schools Committee (1) (Box 23)
    - Schools Committee (2) (Box 23)
    - Schools Committee (3) (Box 24)
    - Schools Committee (4) (Box 24)
    - School Budget (Box 24)
    - Special Committee on Housing (Box 24)
    - Special Committee on Planning and Land Use (Box 24)
    - Evening Star Cup Committee (Box 24)
    - Transportation Committee (Box 24)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Television (Box 24)
    - Siting Process Review Committee, 1993, 1997-1999 (Box 24)
    - Membership Committee, 2008 (Box 24)
  - Subject Files, 1943-1988
    - Airports (Box 24)
    - Airports, Dulles Policy Task Force (Box 24)
    - Arlington Centennial and Bicentennial (Box 24)
    - Arlington County List of Organizations (Box 24)
    - Commission on Arlington's Future (Box 24)
    - Arlington Hall (Box 24)
    - Arlington Night for Newcomers (Box 25)
    - Arlington in Transition Workshop (Box 25)
    - Ashton Heights: Angelica's Restaurant Dance Hall Permit, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Banquet (Box 25)
    - Beautification (Box 25)
    - Cable TV (Box 25)
    - Cancer Society (Box 25)
    - Candidates Meetings (Box 25)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 25)
    - City Charter (Box 25)
    - Circuit Court (Box 25)
    - Colonial Village (Box 25)
    - Commission on Ethics (Box 25)
    - Commissioner of Revenue (Box 25)
    - Commission on Human Resources (Box 25)
    - Commonwealth Attorney (Box 25)
    - Community Chest (Box 25)
    - Condominiums (Box 25)
    - Congress of the United States (1) (Box 25)
    - Congress of the United States (2) (Box 25)
    - Council of Governments (Box 25)
    - Correspondence: Sherman Pratt, 1967 (Box 25)
    - County Board (1) (Box 25)
    - County Board (2) (Box 25)
    - County Board (3) (Box 26)
    - County Budget (Box 26)
    - County Clerk (Box 26)
    - County Court (Box 26)
    - County Fair (Box 26)
    - County Jails (Box 26)
    - County Manager (1) (Box 26)
    - County Manager (2) (Box 26)
    - County Treasurer (Box 26)
    - Courthouse Plaza Project (Box 26)
    - Distinguished and Meritorious Service Award (Box 26)
    - District of Columbia (Box 26)
    - Electoral Board (Box 26)
    - Equal Opportunity Commission (Box 26)
    - Fair Housing Board (Box 26)
    - Federal Agencies (Box 26)
    - Fire Department (Box 26)
    - General Assembly (1) (Box 26)
    - General Assembly (2) (Box 26)
    - Governor (Box 26)
    - Health Department (Box 26)
    - Health Planning (Box 26)
    - Housing, Minimum Standards (Box 26)
    - Housing, Homestead Exemption Act (Box 26)
    - Housing, Miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Inspections Department (Box 26)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 26)
    - Lake Barcroft Public Park (Box 26)
    - League of Women Voters (Box 26)
    - Legislative Issues (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - National Capital Trans. Agency (Box 27)
    - Neighborhood Conservation Plan (Box 27)
    - News Releases (Box 27)
    - Noise Abatement (Box 27)
    - Parade (Box 27)
    - Photographic Documentary Project* (Box 27)
    - Planning Commission (Box 27)
    - Public Safety Department (Box 27)
    - Public Utilities Commission (Box 27)
    - Radio Talks (Box 27)
    - Real Property Assessment Department (Box 27)
    - Recreation Department (Box 27)
    - Safety Council (Box 27)
    - Scholarship Fund (Box 27)
    - Schools, Advisory Committee (Box 27)
    - School Board (Box 27)
    - School Board Candidates (Box 27)
    - School Board Members (Box 27)
    - Schools, Bond Issues (Box 27)
    - School Facilities (Box 27)
    - School Supers' Annual Reports (Box 27)
    - School Superintendent Correspondence (Box 27)
    - School Miscellaneous (Box 27)
    - Sherriff's Department (Box 27)
    - State Board of Education (Box 27)
    - State Department of Conservation and Development (Box 27)
    - State Corporation Commission (Box 27)
    - State Department of Corrections (Box 27)
    - State Highway Commission (Box 27)
    - State Milk Commission (Box 27)
    - State Department of Public Welfare (Box 27)
    - Transportation (Box 27)
    - Tuberculosis Association (Box 28)
    - Virginia Education Commission (Box 28)
    - Voter Registration (Box 28)
    - Washington Gas Light Company (Box 28)
    - Washington, Virginia and Maryland Coach Company (Box 28)
    - Welfare Board of Arlington (Box 28)
    - Zoning Committee Correspondence, 1943-1970 (Box 28)
    - Zoning - County Manager Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 28)
    - Zoning Regulations, 1968-1970 (Box 28)
    - Zoning Reports, 1942-1968 (Box 28)
    - Zoning Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 28)
    - Zoning Reports, no date (Box 28)
    - Zoning Public Notices, 1966-1968 (Box 28)
    - Zoning Public Notices, 1969-1970 (Box 28)
    - Zoning - BZA Minutes, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Zoning - BZA Minutes, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Zoning: Backus vs. BZA Legal Documents (1) (Box 28)
    - Zoning: Backus vs. BZA Legal Documents (2) (Box 28)
    - Zoning: Backus vs. BZA Legal Documents (3) (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Backus vs. BZA Legal Documents (4) (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Backus Research Notes (1) (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Backus Research Notes (2) (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Backus Reference Documents (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Appeals Board Minutes, March - April 1970 (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Appeals Board Minutes, May - June 1970 (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Appeals Board Minutes, August - September 1970 (Box 29)
    - Zoning: Appeals Board Minutes, October - November 1970 (Box 29)
    - Bicentennial Report, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Biographies (Box 29)
    - Databases (Box 29)
    - Delegates College, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Highland Park/Overlee Knolls Civic Association, 2001-2002 (Box 29)
    - Infill, 1997-1999 (1) (Box 29)
    - Infill, 1997-1999 (2) (Box 30)
    - Infill - Residential Study, Interim Report, 1998 (Box 30)
    - National Geographic Article on Arlington, 1953 (Box 30)
    - Neighborhood Day, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Neighborhood Day, 1999 (1) (Box 30)
    - Neighborhood Day, 1999 (2) (Box 30)
    - Northern Virginia Regional Partnership, 1998-2000 (1) (Box 30)
    - Northern Virginia Regional Partnership, 1998-2000 (2) (Box 30)
    - Police (Box 30)
    - Radio Towers (Box 30)